Women Against War; Records apap391
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Yahoo Group Correspondence, 2002-2021
  - OWN Women Against War Action, 2001
    - IFSC event next week; Tent of Abraham, "Stories of Creation" Tuesday, Feb. 10th, Potluck 6-7 PMm Stories 7:15-9 PM, Islamic Center of the Capital District, 2015 February 5
    - Donna Freitas Ph.D. to Speak at UAlbany " Juggling Sexuality, Spirituality, Romance and Religion on America's College Campuses" ,Wednesday, 2/11, 7 PM, Campus Center Ballroom, 2015 February 6
    - Solomon Northup, portrayed by Clifford Oliver, at Albany Institute of History and Art, Thursday, February 12 from 6 to 7 PM, 2015 February 6
    - Moral Monday in Albany: We Are One New York, Topic is Immigration and the Dream Act, State Capitol, Noon to 12:45 PM, 2015 February 7
    - "The Ghost Town" a film aboutconflict in Hebron (with Chomsky and and Sheen), Feb 15th, 2 PM At the Islamic Center of the Capital District, 2015 February 8
    - Reminder to all: Grannies for Peace Valentine"s Day Vigil to be held on Saturday, February 14th from 1 PM to 2 PM at Central Avenue and Wolf Road, 2015 February 8
    - Racial Profiling Documentary, "Profiled" Campaign by Kathleen Foster who did the film on Women"s History in Afghanistan. Indegogo month of February., 2015 February 9
    - Thursday, 2/12, 6:45 - 8:45 PM Film- The Internet's Own Boy: The Story of Aaron Swartz, Bethlehem Public Library, 2015 February 10
    - Black Filmmakers Visit Page Hall, Friday 2/13, 7 PM Screening of "Night Catches Us", 2015 February 10
    - Reaching out on behalf of a A FINAL AREA PERFORMANCE OF GROUNDED: PLEASE SHARE /SAVE THE DATE, 2015 February 10
    - CANCELLED DUE TO FRIGID WEATHER FORECAST!: Grannies for Peace Valentine's Day Vigil scheduled for Saturday, February 14th from 1 PM to 2 PM at Central Avenue and Wolf Road, 2015 February 11
    - KATHY KELLY-Notes From Lexington Federal Prison, 2015 February 11
    - Alternative activity for Grannies, 2015 February 12
    - Fw: [LaVozMagazine] Second Annual Spanish Spelling Bee, and Practice Sessions, now also in Kingston, 2015 February 13
    - Mark Yolles Memorial Service today at FUUSA at 2 PM, 2015 February 15
    - Fw: WAWaction Mark Yolles Memorial Service today at FUUSA at 2 PM, 2015 February 15
    - FreedomF Benefit - blues, classical rock, afro-ska. Saturday, February 21, begins at 7 PM, Road House Grille, Albany, 2015 February 16
    - "Why she ran: A conversation with Women in Politics" Wednesday, February 25th 7 to 8::30 PM Albany, 2015 February 16
    - Albany: Selma 50th Celebration, Saturday, Feb. 28th 1 PM to 3 PM, the Egg, Albany NY, 2015 February 17
    - Film: "ENTRE NOS" Friday, February 27th 8 PM preceeded by a 6:30 PM mixer, AT THE LINDA, Albany NY, 2015 February 17
    - Join us to hear Iranian journalist and author Nazila Fathi speak on March 9th, 2015 February 18
    - Last two days to see the Exhibit on Boycott Campaigns at Siena College. It ends February 20, 2015 February 19
    - Two Important upcoming events: Panel on "Intersectionality", Thursday, March 5th 7 PM to 8 PM, BPL & Talk by Iranian author and journalist Nazila Fathi, Monday, March 9th, 4:30 - 6:30 PM, at Siena College, 2015 March 2
    - Exciting joint event; Friends for Racial Justice and the Interfaith Story Circle-- Friday March 6th, 6 PM to 8:30 PM Albany Friends Meeting House, Please RSVP if possible., 2015 March 3
    - Josh Fox and Zephyr Teachout, Solutions Grassroots Tour: A Solar Home Companion, Saturday, March 7th 7PM, FUUSA, 2015 March 3
    - Important Notice! Homeless Action Committee Sleep-A-Thom In the Park Friday, March 6th - 5 pm - Midnight, 2015 March 4
    - Reminder: Exciting joint event; Friends for Racial Justice and the Interfaith Story Circle, Friday March 6th, 6 PM to 8:30 PM, please RSVP., 2015 March 5
    - "Celebrating All Women": Event for International Women's Day at Opalka Galleries, Sage College at Albany, Sunday March 8th 2 to 5 PM, 2015 March 5
    - Re: WAWaction "Celebrating All Women": Event for International Women's Day at Opalka Galleries, Sage College at Albany, Sunday March 8th 2 to 5 PM, 2015 March 6
    - Netanyahu, the other Israelis and Bobby Burns, from the Peace at Union mailing list, 2015 March 7
    - REMINDER: Iranian journalist and author Nazila Fathi speak at Siena College, Monday, March 9th from 4:30 PM - 6:00 PM, 2015 March 8
    - International Women's Day, 2015 March 8
    - SPRING RISING in Albany, Saratoga, DC & across the Country: An Anti-War Intervention, Sat, Mar 21, 2015 March 9
    - Wonderful and jam packed talk by Iranian Journalist Nazila Fathi at Siena this evening and extended interview with Joe Donohue on WAMC this morning., 2015 March 9
    - GROUNDED at CAPITAL REP on March16th...please help spread the word, 2015 March 10
    - Program about the survival of Greek Jews during WWII, "Song of Life" Saturday, March 14th 1 PM, St. Sophia Community Center, Albany, 2015 March 10
    - Kill the Bills!, 2015 March 10
    - A quick & easy way to ask our Senators to support negotiations with Iran, 2015 March 11
    - IFSC Wednesday, March 25th, 7-9 PM Stories from many diverse Indian Traditions & "GROUNDED" Monday, March 16th, 7 PM, 2015 March 12
    - Spring 2015 Sanctuary season begins next week! Click to read schedule online or to requ a hardcopy., 2015 March 13
    - Invitation to join a Rachel Corrie remembrance vigil, Monday March 16, 4:30 -5:30 PM, Dana Park, Albany NY, 2015 March 14
    - Recent BNP Public Access TV Vide os: Interviews with Joe Lombardo, Angelica Clarke and Mo Hannah, pl us The Forum on Intersectionality, 2015 March 17
    - Women's History Event, Albany City Hall, Wednesday, March 18, 2015 6 PM to 8 PM, 2015 March 17
    - Reminder: Demonstrate for peace this Sat, March 21st, in Albany, Saratoga, & DC, 2015 March 18
    - [undergroundrailroad] Important Dates of Inter and varied events Sunday March 22, through Wednesday, March 25th., 2015 March 19
    - PAUSENERGY Earth Day Lawn SIgn. Action for Earth Day and every day, 2015 March 19
    - March 29 at Social Justice Center: Film about Israeli settlements, 2015 March 19
    - Clarification on date for film: March 22, 2015 March 20
    - Please Share as a reminder about this afternoon: Demonstrate for peace this Sat, March 21st, in Albany, Saratoga, & DC, 2015 March 21
    - Women on 20s.org and PAUSENERGY Earth Day Lawn SIgn. Action for Earth Day and every day, 2015 March 21
    - We made it! Thanks for helping us raise $25,000! Kathleen Foster's documentary "Profiled" about racial profiling and police brutality is now fully funded., 2015 March 22
    - Just published a photo essay with Mabel's pictures of Saturday's Wolf Road, "End Endless Wars" demonstration. Here's the link:, 2015 March 24
    - Celebrate the Activism of Barbara Smith -- Panel discussion and book signing with Barbara, Tuesday, March 31, 2015 March 25
    - WAWaction Women on 20s.org and PAUSENERGY Earth Day Lawn SIgn. Action for Earth Day and every day, 2015 March 25
    - "Cuba: An African Odyssey"- "Political-historical documentary making at its b!" Monday 3/30 6pm, Albany Public Library, 2015 March 26
    - Important Anti-Nuke Activity in NYC April 27 around the NPT Conference & Please SIGN PETITION to abolish nuclear weapons, 2015 March 30
    - Grannies for Peace & others: Change of place for First Wednesday Peace Vigil. Wednesday, April 1st. Join Protect our People energy rally in front of City Hall, Albany, 11:45 through 1 PM, 2015 March 30
    - Film: "The Black Power Mixtapes" 1967-1975, Thursday, April 2nd 6:45 - 8:45 PM, Bethlehem Public Library., 2015 March 31
    - Women Against War endorses the Peace & Planet Mobilization, 2015 April 1
    - [unac] Join the Cuban 5 at the UNAC conference! Early registration extended until April 8th., 2015 April 1
    - Join Us on Earth Day 2015 to Prot US Military Climate Druction, 2015 April 2
    - Apology To The People of Viet Nam, 2015 April 4
    - Lecture: "A Muslim Perspective on Religious Extremism and Terrorism" Tuesday, April 14, 5:30 PM to 7:30 PM, Campus Center, Assembly Hall at UAlbany, 2015 April 5
    - A Woman's Place is on the Money!, 2015 April 8
    - Fw: [upstatedroneaction] Author Frida Berrigan @ Buffalo St. Books, Ithaca NY, Tuesday, 4/14, 6 PM, 2015 April 8
    - Fw: Petition asking the UN Security Council to take actions against Saudi Arabia to stop the druction of Yemen & some background information., 2015 April 9
    - The Stephen and Harriet Myers Residence - Open House, Sunday, April 19, Noon to 3 PM as part of the Underground Railroad history Conference, April 17 -19, 2015 April 9
    - Fw: I just signed this important petition against war with Iran -- will you?, 2015 April 9
    - Reminder: Lecture: Religious Extremism and Terrorism by Imam Ibrahim SayarTomorrow, April 14 at 5:30 through 7:30 PM Campus Center UAlbany-Turkish Refreshments., 2015 April 13
    - EARTH DAY - APRIL 22: EPA TO THE PENTAGON: STOP ENVIRONMENTAL ECOCIDE, 2015 April 14
    - UNAC national conference - Stop the Wars at Home and Abroad May 8-10, Secaucus, NJ, 2015 April 14
    - "Why Israel should support diplomacy with Iran" talk Monday, 4/27 at 7:30 PM, B'nai Shalom synagogue, Albany, 2015 April 14
    - WAWaction The Stephen and Harriet Myers Residence - Open House, Sunday, April 19, Noon to 3 PM as part of the Underground Railroad history Conference, April 17 -19, 2015 April 15
    - Please sign Judy Bello's petition calling for an end to the Saudi bombing in Yemen before she brings it to the UN Security Council this Friday!, 2015 April 15
    - Sunday, May 3rd dinner honoring Rev John Paarlberg for Israel/Paline work, doors open at 3 PM, Dinner at 4 PM, 2015 April 16
    - Saturday, April 18, Peace vigil at Noon, Peace Walk until 3 PM and potluck at 6 PM, Peace walkers coming to SARATOGA SPRINGS., 2015 April 17
    - Blog post on Yemen, 2015 April 17
    - Please save the date for our "Racism Breaks Grannies' Hearts" vigil at the Tulip F, Saturday, May 9th from 1 PM to 2 PM with optional leafleting from 2 PM to 2:30 PM, 2015 April 17
    - Vatican Ends Battle With U.S. C atholic Nuns Group - NYTimes.com, 2015 April 18
    - Join us next week to HALT Solitary in NY: Statewide conference call, Tuesday, April 21, Lobbying in Albany, Wednesday April 2. and more information, 2015 April 18
    - The UAlbany Interfaith Center Peace Celebration, Monday, April 20, 5 PM Celebrating the Peace walkers in the NPT Walk, Peace prayers, blessings, poems, readings., 2015 April 19
    - Re: WAWaction Join us next week to HALT Solitary in NY: Statewide conference call, Tuesday, April 21, Lobbying in Albany, Wednesday April 2. and more information, 2015 April 20
    - Reminder: Join Us this Earth Day 2015, Noon to 1 PM to Prot US Military Climate Druction, 2015 April 20
    - Jun San"s NPT Peace Walk is looking for one more car/driver tomorrow., 2015 April 20
    - Fw: Children at the Well Youth Storytellers, Story Circle,Thursday, April 23rd, 6:30 to 8:30 PM -- 10th Anniversary performance and potluck Sunday. April 26th, 2 PM FUUSA, 405 Washington Avenue, Albany, 2015 April 21
    - Fw: Film Screening: "Love is a Verb" Thursday, April 23rd, 6PM Roger Bacon Hall, Siena College, Turkish refreshments., 2015 April 22
    - Earth Day 2015: We speak out on Militarism and Climate Change, 2015 April 23
    - Fw: Connect to Peace & PlanetConference, Friday April 24th and Saturday, April 25th, from wherever you are! Live streaming., 2015 April 24
    - Fw: Move On petition to President Obama on Saudi bombing of Yemen, please sign and/or call him during the week., 2015 April 25
    - Friday, May 1st. Full Day of May Day celebratory events from 6 am through 10 PM, Sanctuary for Independent Media and other locations in Albany and Troy., 2015 April 27
    - review of Grounded, 2015 April 27
    - An Intersection of the Peace and Justice Movement, U NAC Conference Friday, May 8 " Sunday, May 10, 2015, 2015 April 28
    - Report from Joy First on an Earth Day action at the EPA and the Pentagon by the National Committee on Nonviolent Resistance, 2015 April 28
    - Please Stand With Us at our "Racism Breaks Grannies' Hearts" vigil, at the Tulip F, Saturday, May 9th from 1 PM to 2 PM. Optional leafleting from 2 PM to 2:30 PM, 2015 April 29
    - WAW Activists - Please sign our petition on Yemen!, 2015 April 29
    - Peace Speakers on Anniversary of Vietnam War, Friday, May 15, 2015, 7 -8:45 PM, Bethlehem Town Library, 2015 April 29
    - Color of Change Petition: #JusticeForFreddieGray, 2015 April 30
    - Tomorrow: Sunday May 3rd - "African American Albany: 1847-1875" 194 Livingston Avenue, Albany, 5 PM through 7 PM, 2015 May 2
    - Women's Coffee Night in recognition of Mother's Day, Saturday, May 9th at 6:30 PM, Turkish Community Center., 2015 May 3
    - Please join us for an Informational Picket of John Bolton's appearance! Tuesday, May 5th from 6-7 PM. Union College Memorial Chapel, 2015 May 4
    - Fw: Divided Families Official Petition! White House Petition on reuniting Korean families, 2015 May 5
    - Celebrate with The Interfaith Alliance of NYS, 2015 May 5
    - Fw: Global Fair Trade Market at Albany School of Humanities Saturday May 9th from 10 am to 3 PM, 2015 May 5
    - Fw: Just published a blog article about John Bolton's appearance -preceded by a creative, collaborative, counter informational picketm at Union College, on Tuesday, May 5th., 2015 May 7
    - Fw: [unac] The UNAC conference [Friday, May 8 - Sunday, May 10, 2015] will be LIVE STREAMED., 2015 May 8
    - Contemporary Art in Iran Talk by Joydeep Roy-Bhattacharya, who is also a novelist: Tuesday, May 12, Karp Hall, Union College, 4 PM to 5:30 PM, 2015 May 11
    - The Vietnam War, "40 Years Later." Friday, May 15th 7 - 8:45 PM, Bethlehem Public Library, Larry Wittner and Dan Wilcox, 2015 May 12
    - Demonstration Sunday 5/17 in Saratoga Springs, NY PLEASE SHARE & POST, 2015 May 13
    - Drone Alert Hudson Valley Memorial Day Weekend event, Sunday, May 24, at 3 PM Peace Park behind Village Hall, New Paltz, 2015 May 16
    - Transform Now Plowshares Civil Resisters, Sr. Megan, Michael and Greg are out of prison!, 2015 May 17
    - Spring 2015 Newsletter for Jajja's Kids. Spring Fund raiser Friday, May 29th 5 to 9 PM, Arts Center of the Capital Region, Troy, 2015 May 17
    - In Prison, But Not Forgotten: NCPCF' s Fourth Annual Ramadan Gifts Campaign, 2015 May 18
    - Fw: Union College, Art for Change Event one day only, Tomorrow, Wednesday, 5/20, outside Schaffer Library from 12:50 PM to 5 PM, 2015 May 20
    - Invitation to join the Memorial Day Parade in the Veteran's for Peace contingent, Monday May 25th at 9 am/step off at 9:30 am, Central Ave. & Partridge St., 2015 May 22
    - Fw: Who is in the way of Peace? Message and requ from the Women's delegation to cross the DMZ on Sunday, May 24th., 2015 May 23
    - Fw: Invitation to Photography opening and exhibit of images from Honduras, Wesley Community senior care, Saratoga, May 2 through June 1, 2015, 2015 May 24
    - "The Koch Brothers Exposed, 2014" followed by a discussion with the film's director. Wednesday, June 3, 7 - 8:45 PM, Bethlehem Public Library, 2015 May 26
    - Talk by author and journalist Chris Hedges, Friday, May 29, 7 PM, Sanctuary for Independent Media, [Fund raising dinner preceeding the talk from 5 PM to 6:30 PM], 2015 May 26
    - UNAC at Left Forum, Free Oscar Lopez Rivera, prots against US drone base in Germany, The Saudi/US complete DRUCTION of the port in Yemen where the Red Crescent rescue ship was about to land., 2015 May 27
    - Can our prison system be transformed?, 2015 May 29
    - Petition to President Obama on Nuclear Weapons: "Lead us to a world free of Nuclear Weapons!", 2015 May 29
    - Talks by Steve Ellner at Union College, Wednesday June 3rd: 12:55 PM "Pizza and Politics"-Dinner talk at 5:30 PM. THURSDAY June 4th, 7 PM,James Conolly Forum, Oakwood Community Center, Troy, 2015 May 29
    - June 2nd is the first "National Gun Violence Awareness Day." Sign the pledge: Wear orange June 2nd to fight gun violence, 2015 May 31
    - Support of Our Muslim Sisters and Brothers in Arizona, 2015 May 31
    - Fw: Context for Linda LeTendre's call for individual and group support of the members of the Phoenix Islamic Community Center after the prot on Friday during evening prayers., 2015 June 1
    - Good Kill, movie about drone pilot, 2015 June 1
    - Women Against War message of support to the Islamic Community Center in Tempe, Arizona, 2015 June 2
    - Fw: Wednesday, June 3 at 7:00, The Koch Brothers Exposed 2014, 2015 June 2
    - Fw: [LaVozMagazine] Despidos de inmigrant es de Ideal Snacks,Liberty + Leo Genovese y los Legal Aliens + Vivir en New Paltz, Hippie Town y mucho ms en La Voz de junio, 2015 June 3
    - TIANYS MEETING June 8, 2015, 9 am, with Mark Mishler, Brad Hansen and Judith Brink. Good information about criminal justice reform and community policing., 2015 June 5
    - "Love is a Verb" Showing at the William K. Sanford Town Library, Latham, Thursday, 6/11/15 at 6 PM,, Free Event, Refreshments, please RSVP, 2015 June 8
    - "Gaza FreedomFlotilla Three", News of progress from Sweden and goals., 2015 June 9
    - Closing event of the Sanctuary's spring season: Freedom Fival Saturday, 6/13 from 3 to 6 PM. Free Food, music and art activities....., 2015 June 11
    - Juneteenth Celebration this Sunday, 1-6PM & Black Arts and Cultural Fival, August 1st, Noon -7PM, 2015 June 12
    - 15th annual Juneteenth Celebration June 19-20 Schenectady, sponsored by the Hamilton Hill Arts Center, 2015 June 12
    - Good Code Pink analysis and petition on Iraq: 7 Ways to Deal with ISIS, 2015 June 12
    - Grannies for Peace: Invitation to Stories for Racial Healing: Fri, June 26, 2015, 5:30 PM, 2015 June 14
    - Welcome the Pastors for Peace Friendshipment Caravan, Tuesday, June 30th, 5:30 to 8:30 PM First Presbyterian Church, Albany., 2015 June 15
    - Buy Your Tickets Now! NCPCF Ramadan Iftar Fundraiser, "Targeting Muslims: St ate Violence in the War on Terror", Su nday, June 28th, 6:30 PM, Washington DC., 2015 June 15
    - Fw: Kathy Kelly on CounterPunch Radio and more, 2015 June 17
    - WAWaction Grannies for Peace: Invitation to Stories for Racial Healing: Fri, June 26, 2015, 5:30 PM, 2015 June 17
    - VOLUNTEERS NEEDED FOR SUMMER YOUTH EMPLOYMENT PROGRAM - FOUR FRIDAYS IN JULY. Orientation/training during the week of June for about an hour during the week of June 29th., 2015 June 18
    - Vigil Tonight For The Murdered Church Prayer Group - Saratoga Springs, 2015 June 18
    - Fw: FRIENDSHIPMENT CARAVAN.2015 Two events and many ways to help: June 30, 5:30 PM pot luck and speaker, July 1, 8 am breakfast ,conversation and loading the van with aid items., 2015 June 19
    - Fw: Monday, 6/22 in Albany: Fast Food Workers Wage Board Rally and Hearing, Rally at 9 am.Hearing begins at 10am and lasts until 2 )M, 2015 June 20
    - Fw: How you can take Action for Charlon:, 2015 June 20
    - End Racism Vigil Monday from 5 PM to 6 PM, 4 Corners, Delmar Peace and Justice advocates invited!, 2015 June 21
    - Stories for Racial Healing Fri. 6/26 Albany Friends Meeting, 5:30 PM refreshments & registration, 6:30 to 8:30 PM stories and discussion, 2015 June 22
    - A photo essay and brief description of yerday's Bethlehem Neighbors for Peace vigil - with Grannies, MoveOn and other community visitors., 2015 June 23
    - Tomorrow: Thursday, June 25th 6 PM 1st Israel AME, Albany, Service of Remembrance and Hope. Flyer attached., 2015 June 24
    - Fw: [LaVozMagazine] Another award, and an invitation / Otro premio, y una invitacin, 2015 June 25
    - Very clear and important case of FBI entrapment: Please help publicize: Three pieces on the Fort Dix Five case published yerday (Thursday, 6/25/15), 2015 June 26
    - #FreedomFlotilla Sets Sail; Urge Kerry to Oppose Attack, 2015 June 27
    - Rally against Racism, Economic Inequality and War - July 25, 2015 June 27
    - Film about the future of the rise of the Corporate State "Obey" Thursday, July 2, 7 to 8:45 PM, Bethlehem Public Library. Discussion to follow., 2015 June 29
    - Film:"TheFilm: "Yes Men are Revolting" showing at Proctors GE Theater, Tuesday, June 30th and Wednesday July 1st at 3:30, 5:30 and 7:30 PM each day., 2015 June 29
    - Fw: August 14 and 15th, 2015 An event not to be missed!, 2015 June 30
    - Fw: Parking at the Lac-Megantic rally tomorrow MONDAY 11;45 Albany if you are available, 2015 July 6
    - The Charlon Church Shooting: Sowing seeds of hope, forgiveness, faith and love in the midst of despair, 2015 July 6
    - RSVP Reminder for Thursday, July 9, 2015 Ramadan Program and Dinner at The Interfaith Center, UAlbany, 2015 July 7
    - Vigil to mark 1-yr anniversary of Israeli war against Gaza: Thursday, July 16, 5:30 PM, Dana Park, Albany, 2015 July 8
    - Book Signing on July 24 Will Mark Publication o f Former Prisoners Memoir, 2015 July 8
    - Free three part film series marks atomic bombings and calls for nuclear abolition -- Tuesday, 8/4, Niskayuna, Wednesday,8/5, Delmar, Monday, 8/10, Albany. Details below:, 2015 July 9
    - Call for Sanity on 60th anniversary of Russell-Einstein Manifo,petition and statements by some original signers, 2015 July 9
    - 2015 PEACE FAIR INVITATION, 2015 July 11
    - Save the Date for the Third North Star Interfaith Peace Walk, Sunday, September 27th at 2 PM in Albany, 2015 July 12
    - Pasta and meatball dinner this Friday! Please join us., 2015 July 13
    - Peacock in Troy on Friday, July 31st, 2015 July 13
    - Reminder: Vigil to mark 1 year anniversary of Israeli war against Gaza: Tomorrow, Thursday, 7/16 from 5:30 to 7 PM, Dana Park, Albany, 2015 July 15
    - Iran deal a victory for diplomacy! Thank you to all who helped get us to this day!, 2015 July 15
    - Storytelling Home Concert 8/2, 2015 July 15
    - Schenectady Peace Pole Walk - August 6th, 2015 July 15
    - Annual reading of John Hersey's "Hiroshima" Thursday, August 6, 11 am, Townsend Park, Albany. People encouraged to read or to listen., 2015 July 17
    - "Drones Fly, Children Die" Gathering at Hancock Air Base, Syracuse Sunday 7/26, 9 am to 11 am, overnight hospitality available. Link to a flyer with more details, 2015 July 17
    - Schenectady Peace Pole Walk -Thursday, August 6th- CORRECTIONS in RED, 2015 July 17
    - Monday, August 3, Starting at 5:30 PM - 11th Anniversary Commemoration of the Arrs of Yassin Aref & Mohammed Hossain [Rally, Speakers, Dinner, March and Movie], 2015 July 18
    - Aug. 6 Peace Walk Commemoration, 2015 July 18
    - [undergroundrailroad] Young Abolitionist Institute Open House, Thursday, July 30th from 2 PM to 4 PM, at the Stephen and Harriet Myers Residence, Albany, 2015 July 20
    - annual commemoration of Aref-Hossain arrs on August 3: rally, march, film, 2015 July 20
    - Fw: [unac-nyc] Saturday, July 25, Million People's March - take the Path train with others from NYC, 2015 July 21
    - Reminder: [upstatedroneaction] "Drones Fly Children Die" Vigil This Sunday, July 26 at Hancock Air Base, 2015 July 21
    - KATERI 17: A CELEBRATION OF UNITY, COMMUNITY AND PEACE - A PERSONAL INVITATION...PLEASE SHARE, 2015 July 21
    - Singing for Peace & Justice: Joe Hill Road Show, Thursday, July 30, 7 PM, Proctors, Schenectady., 2015 July 22
    - Call for action as AIPAC and MEK join forces?! Current reports are that Congressional offices are receiving calls 10 to 1 AGAINST approving the Joint Comprehensive Plan of Action, 2015 July 23
    - Event Invitation: Say Her Name: Call For Justice & Vigil For Women of Color Lost To State Violence, 2015 July 23
    - REMINDER: Book Signing Tomorrow, 7/24, Wi ll Mark Publication of Former Prisoners Memo ir, 2015 July 23